Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Competitive Advertisements, Pre-55 Group, 1894-1957
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Household Goods
    - Furniture
      - Modernage, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 157)
      - Pullman Couch, 1949-1951, (3 folders) (Box 157)
    - Floor Covering
      - Linoleum and tile, 1948 (Box 157)
    - Laundry and Detergents
      - Fab, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 157)
      - Fels Naptha, 1946-1954, (7 folders) (Box 157)
      - Fels Naptha, 1926-1951, (20 folders) (Box 158)
      - Fels Naptha, 1923-1924, (2 folders) (Box 159)
      - Glim, 1949-1951, (3 folders) (Box 159)
      - Ivory, 1939-1952, (19 folders) (Box 159)
      - Ivory, 1937-1939, (4 folders) (Box 160)
      - Rinso, 1927-1933, (6 folders) (Box 160)
      - Silk Eze, 1930 (Box 160)
      - Silver Dust, 1947-1953, (6 folders) (Box 160)
      - Silver Dust, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 161)
      - Soapine, 1925 (Box 161)
      - Surf, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 161)
      - Super Suds, 1943-1954, (9 folders) (Box 161)
      - Super Suds, 1932-1942, (8 folders) (Box 162)
      - Surf, 1949-1950, (3 folders) (Box 162)
      - Swan, 1942-1952, (12 folders) (Box 162)
      - Swerl, 1949-1952, (4 folders) (Box 162)
      - Tag, 1953 (Box 162)
      - Tag, 1942-1952, (10 folders) (Box 163)
      - Tide, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 163)
    - Ranges and stoves, 1944-1954, (11 folders) (Box 163)
    - Refrigerators, 1943-1951, (8 folders) (Box 163)
    - Refrigerators, 1949 (Box 164)
    - Rubber goods, 1943-1954, (10 folders) (Box 164)
    - Sewing Machines
      - Miscellaneous, 1940-1952, (11 folders) (Box 164)
      - Singer, 1940-1941, (2 folders) (Box 164)
      - White, 1941 (Box 164)
    - Silver and Silverware
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (11 folders) (Box 164)
      - Community, 1948-1954, (6 folders) (Box 164)
      - Community, 1947 (Box 165)
      - Alvin, 1948-1953, (6 folders) (Box 165)
      - Gorham, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 165)
      - Holmes & Edwards, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 165)
      - International Sterling, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 165)
      - Lunt, 1951-1954, (3 folders) (Box 165)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 165)
      - Lunt, 1948-1950, (3 folders) (Box 166)
      - Reed & Barton, 1953 (Box 166)
      - 1847 Rogers Bros., 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 166)
      - Towle, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 166)
      - Wallace Sterling, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 166)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 166)
  - Tobacco Products
    - Pipe and Loose Tobacco
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1946 (Box 167)
      - Kentucky Club, 1949-1953 (Box 167)
      - Christian Pepper, Dr. Grabow, C.B. Weber, John Middleton, 1947-1948 (Box 167)
      - George Washington, Philip Morris Revelation, Dill's Best, John Middleton, 1947 (Box 167)
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1945-1948 (Box 167)
      - Sir Walter Raleigh/Old Gold, 1944-1954, (2 folders) (Box 167)
      - Country Doctor, 1944-1947 (Box 167)
      - Briggs, 1945 (Box 167)
      - Prince Albert, 1947-1950, (2 folders) (Box 167)
      - Edgeworth, 1949 (Box 167)
      - Kentucky Club, 1954, (2 folders) (Box 167)
      - Prince Albert, 1948-1954, (3 folders) (Box 167)
      - Half & Half, 1926 (Box 167)
      - Buckingham, Half & Half, 1926-1927 (Box 167)
      - Model, Old Briar, 1953-1954 (Box 167)
      - Edgeworth, 1948-1954 (Box 167)
      - Rum and Maple, Tobin (Cookie Jar, Irish American), Christian Peper (Crosby Square, London Dock, Peper's), 1943 (Box 168)
      - Yello-Bole, Alfred Dunhill, Rogers Imports, Dobie's Four Square, Kirsten, Kent, 1944-1953 (Box 168)
      - Briggs, Indian House, 1946-1954 (Box 168)
      - Bond Street, Country Doctor, John Middleton, Old Virginia, 1943 (Box 168)
      - Model, Bugler, Smoker's Haven/Lord Clive, Swan Ries, 1943 (Box 168)
      - Liggett & Myers/Granger, Spud Imperial, 1943 (Box 168)
      - Edgeworth, Revelation, 1943 (Box 168)
      - Briggs, Prince Albert, 1940-1943 (Box 168)
      - Crosby Square, London Dock, Whitehall, Sportsman, Brindley, Sugar Barrel, India House, Daniel Webster, 1944-1946 (Box 168)
      - George Washington, Granger, Camel, Prince Albert, Holiday, 1944-1949 (Box 168)
      - John Middleton, 1944-1946 (Box 168)
      - Rum and Maple, John Surrey, Snow Apple, Brush Creek, John Middleton, Sutliff Tobacco/Heine's, 1944-1945 (Box 168)
      - Revelation, Bond Street, 1944-1948, (2 folders) (Box 168)
      - Bond Street, Havana, Tampa, Rum and Maple, Zippo, Holiday, 1949-1957 (Box 168)
      - Rum and Maple, Sir Walter Raleigh, Wedgewood, El Roi-Tan, Holiday, 1944-1949 (Box 168)
      - Irish Castle, Donniford, Bergamot, Canadian Plug, Dill's Best, 1945-1948 (Box 168)
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1945 (Box 168)
    - Cigars
      - Blackstone, 1940-1945, (5 folders) (Box 169)
      - Admiration, 1940-1953, (12 folders) (Box 169)
      - Dutch Masters, 1941-1945, (5 folders) (Box 170)
    - Cigarettes--Cavalier, 1952 (Box 170)
    - Cigars
      - Cinco, 1946-1947 (Box 170)
      - Blackstone, 1944-1947 (Box 170)
      - El Producto, 1946-1947, (4 folders) (Box 171)
      - Dunhill, 1940 (Box 171)
      - Dutch Masters, 1943-1954, (7 folders) (Box 171)
      - El Producto, 1941-1948, (12 folders) (Box 172)
      - I. Lewis, 1943 (Box 172)
      - R.G. Dunn, 1944 (Box 172)
      - El Producto, 1949-1953, (4 folders) (Box 173)
      - Rey del Rey, 1944-1948 (Box 174)
      - Phillies, 1940-1952, (11 folders) (Box 174)
      - Harvester, 1954 (Box 174)
      - Robt. Burns, 1940-1954, (12 folders) (Box 175)
      - Zippo, 1950 (Box 175)
      - Virginia Rounds, 1950 (Box 175)
      - Admiration, 1943 (Box 175)
      - Dutch Masters, 1946 (Box 176)
      - Royalist, 1943-1947, (6 folders) (Box 176)
      - Tudor Arms, 1939-1942 (Box 176)
      - Van Dyck, 1941 (Box 176)
      - Webster, 1940-1952, (8 folders) (Box 176)
      - Cinco, 1945 (Box 176)
      - Macy's Havana Humidor, 1940 (Box 176)
      - Zippo, 1944 (Box 176)
      - White Owl, 1940 (Box 176)
      - Admiration, Van Dyck, Seidenberg, Harvester, Haddon Hall, 1948-1949 (Box 177)
      - Rialto, Gold Label, R.G. Dunn, Muriel, 1948 (Box 177)
      - La Magnita, Dexter, Havana Dunhill, Prince Hamlet, La Palina, Garcia Grande, El Producto, 1948-1950 (Box 177)
      - La Magnita, Harvester, Gold Label, 1949-1950 (Box 177)
      - Van Dyck, Prince Hamlet, Haddon Hall, 1949-1950 (Box 177)
      - Gold Label, El Producto, La Palina, Perfecto, Garcia y Vega, Nat Sherman, 1954 (Box 177)
      - Robt. Burns, White Owl, Cigar Institute of America, Dunhill, 1950-1953 (Box 177)
      - Gold Label, Mart, Van Dyck, The American, Havana Dunhill,, 1951 (Box 177)
      - La Magnita, El Producto, Haddon Hall, Seidenberg, 1951 (Box 177)
      - Harvester, White Owl, 1951 (Box 177)
      - Reyes Havana Blunts, Nat Sherman Gold Label, Haddon Hall, Havana Dunhill, La Primadore, Joseph Jones, Garcia y Vega, 1952-1953 (Box 177)
      - Cigar Institute of America, Gold Label, Harvester, 1952-1953 (Box 177)
      - Royalton, King Edward, Wedgewood, Garcia y Vega, 1943 (Box 177)
      - Webster, Havana Dunhill, 1943 (Box 177)
      - Dutch Masters, Natural Bloom, J.A., Flamingo, Haddon Hall, La Coronada, Y-B, 1943 (Box 177)
      - Robt. Burns, Rey del Rey, 1943 (Box 177)
      - Dexter, Yankee, R.G. Sullivan's, La Palina, 1943 (Box 177)
      - Dunhill, Dutch Masters, Prince Albert, Kind Edward, Nat Sherman, Garcia y Vega, 1945-1946 (Box 178)
      - Cinco, Robt. Burns, 1943-1947 (Box 178)
      - La Primador, Royalist, Santa Fe, Garcia Grande, John Ruskin, Dry Climate, J.A., 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Stetson, Kentucky Club, Dunhill, Roi-Tan, 1947-1950 (Box 178)
      - Garcia y Vega, Seidenberg, La Magnita, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Habanello, Natural Bloom, Muriel, La Palina, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Air-Flo, Van Dyck, White Owl, Dutch Masters, Y-B, M&O, Nat Sherman, Seeman's, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Ignacio Haya, Tom Palmer, Bankable, Ameera, BCM, Coronada, Kilby, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Dexter, 7-204, Peter Schuyler, R.G. Dunn, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Robt. Burns, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
      - Amerada, Haddon Hall, 1945-1947 (Box 178)
    - Cigarettes
      - Camel, 1933-1934, (6 folders) (Box 179)
      - Camel, 1926-1933, (5 folders) (Box 180)
      - Camel, 1935, (2 folders) (Box 181)
      - Cavalier, 1949-1954, (5 folders) (Box 181)
      - Chelsea, 1943-1953, (10 folders) (Box 181)
      - Chesterfield, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 181)
      - Deities, 1939 (Box 181)
      - Domino, 1936-1942, (2 folders) (Box 181)
      - Dunhill, 1939 (Box 181)
      - Du Maurier, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 181)
      - Chesterfield, 1924-1930, (9 folders) (Box 182)
      - Chesterfield, 1944-1951, (8 folders) (Box 183)
      - Du Maurier, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 184)
      - Embassy, 1949 (Box 184)
      - Fatima, 1922-1953, (9 folders) (Box 184)
      - Fleetwood, 1942-1945, (4 folders) (Box 184)
      - Julep, 1942 (Box 184)
      - Kent, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 184)
      - Kentucky Winner, 1934-1935 (Box 184)
      - Kool, 1933-1934, (4 folders) (Box 184)
      - Kool, 1945-1951, (7 folders) (Box 185)
      - Lucky Strike, 1948-1952, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - Smokers Articles
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 185)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Baby Accessories, 1930-1931 (Box 185)
    - Appliances: Mennen, 1932 (Box 185)
    - Medicine: Mennen, 1930 (Box 185)
    - Dennison, 1932 (Box 185)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 185)
    - Toilet Articles, 1928-1929 (Box 185)
    - Soap, 1922-1927 (Box 185)
    - Barber Shops--Terminal, 1936-1941, (5 folders) (Box 185)
  - Tobacco Products
    - Cigarettes
      - L&M, 1954 (Box 186)
      - Life, 1948 (Box 186)
      - Lords, 1953 (Box 186)
      - Lucky Strike, 1946-1950, (5 folders) (Box 186)
      - Kool, 1937-1944, (8 folders) (Box 186)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 187)
    - Smokers Articles
      - Dunhill, 1947 (Box 187)
      - Kaywoodie Briar, 1944-1954, (11 folders) (Box 187)
      - Lektrolite, 1944-1947, (3 folders) (Box 187)
      - Ronson Lighter, 1945-1954, (10 folders) (Box 187)
      - Yello-Bole,, 1944-1953, (7 folders) (Box 187)
      - Zippo Windproof Lighter, 1944-1954, (11 folders) (Box 187)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Barber Shops
      - Terminal, 1920-1933, (2 folders) (Box 188)
    - Bath Preparations, 1940-1954, (13 folders) (Box 188)
    - Bath Salts
      - Bathasweet, 1919-1939, (2 folders) (Box 188)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1939, (4 folders) (Box 188)
    - Brushes and Combs (includes toothbrushes)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1953, (8 folders) (Box 188)
      - D.D., 1940 (Box 188)
      - Hutax, 1928 (Box 188)
      - Pepsodent, 1941 (Box 188)
      - Allbright, 1924-1925 (Box 188)
    - Tissues, Cleansing
      - Kleenex, 1946 (Box 188)
  - Tobacco Products
    - Cigarettes
      - Lucky Strike, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 189)
      - Marlboro, 1952 (Box 189)
      - Marvels; Marlboro, 1945-1953 (Box 189)
      - Viceroys, 1950-1957 (Box 190)
      - King Sano, 1954 (Box 190)
      - Tareyton, 1920-1936, (3 folders) (Box 190)
      - Viceroys, 1936-1957, (4 folders) (Box 190)
      - Winston, 1954 (Box 190)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1953, (3 folders) (Box 190)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1939, (17 folders) (Box 191)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1950, (15 folders) (Box 192)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Combs, 1941 (Box 193)
    - Cold Creams
      - Cheramy, 1926 (Box 193)
      - Colgates, 1915-1922 (Box 193)
      - Colonial Dames, 1936-1937 (Box 193)
      - Coty, 1930 (Box 193)
      - Black and White, 1927 (Box 193)
      - Boncilla Lemon Magnesia, 1928-1931 (Box 193)
      - Dr. Charles Flesh Food, 1931 (Box 193)
      - Caron, 1939-1940 (Box 193)
    - Compacts, 1940-1941 (Box 193)
    - Beauty Specialists and Beauty Preparations
      - Amor Skin, 1928-1929, (2 folders) (Box 193)
      - Arden, 1929-1947 (Box 193)
      - Armand, 1930-1931 (Box 193)
      - Harriet Hubbard Ayer, 1930-1953, (14 folders) (Box 193)
      - Bourjois, 1931-1942, (7 folders) (Box 193)
      - Bertie, 1928-1930 (Box 193)
      - Botany Lanolin, 1943 (Box 193)
      - Caron, 1933 (Box 193)
      - Chanel, 1942 (Box 193)
      - Charles on the Ritz, 1927-1930 (Box 193)
      - Cheramy, 1928-1941, (3 folders) (Box 193)
      - Colgates, 1927 (Box 193)
      - Creme Nerol, 1920 (Box 193)
      - Coty, 1939-1953, (3 folders) (Box 194)
      - Covermark, 1938 (Box 194)
      - Daggett & Ramsdell, 1935-1936, (2 folders) (Box 194)
      - Denton's Facial Magnesia, 1929-1930 (Box 194)
      - Francis Denny, 1943 (Box 194)
      - Dermetics, 1941 (Box 194)
      - Djer Kiss, 1928-1931, (3 folders) (Box 194)
      - Domino House, 1922 (Box 194)
      - Carolyn Drew, 1933 (Box 194)
      - DuBerry, 1941-1944 (Box 194)
      - Dumas, 1932 (Box 194)
      - Duart, 1935-1936 (Box 194)
      - Marie Earle, 1928-1941, (3 folders) (Box 194)
      - Early American, 1939-1952, (13 folders) (Box 194)
      - Elmo, 1941 (Box 194)
      - Embassy, 1934 (Box 194)
      - Frederics, 1928-1934, (7 folders) (Box 194)
      - Frigidine, 1927-1929, (2 folders) (Box 194)
      - Barbara Gould, 1930-1950, (9 folders) (Box 194)
      - Dorothy Gray, 1948 (Box 194)
      - Harper Method, 1928-1934, (2 folders) (Box 194)
      - Hinds, 1930-1932, (3 folders) (Box 194)
      - Edna Wallace Hopper, 1950 (Box 195)
      - Houbigant, 1926-1947, (12 folders) (Box 195)
      - Richard Hudnut (including DuBarry Success School), 1931-1951, (8 folders) (Box 195)
      - Jergens, 1950 (Box 195)
      - Jonteel, 1933 (Box 195)
      - Kissproof, 1930 (Box 195)
      - Krank, 1930-1931 (Box 195)
      - Lady Esther, 1931-1950, (7 folders) (Box 195)
      - Lavena, 1936 (Box 195)
      - Lentheric, 1934-1939 (Box 195)
      - Lucien Lelong, 1940-1941, (2 folders) (Box 195)
      - R. Louis, 1928-1933 (Box 195)
      - Lucille Young, 1929 (Box 195)
      - Mme Bertie, 1930-1931 (Box 195)
      - Madame Vaquet, 1931-1932 (Box 195)
      - Manuel, 1928-1931 (Box 195)
      - Marinello, 1925-1931 (Box 195)
      - Marly, 1931 (Box 195)
      - Mavis, 1928 (Box 195)
      - Max Factor, 1931-1953, (18 folders) (Box 196)
      - Melba, 1929 (Box 196)
      - Mercolized Wax Cream, 1933-1950, (8 folders) (Box 196)
      - Mineralava, 1923-1924 (Box 196)
      - Milk Bath, 1936 (Box 196)
      - Miner's, 1940-1942, (2 folders) (Box 196)
      - Mitcham Lavender, 1933 (Box 196)
      - Germaine Monteil, 1942 (Box 196)
      - Nestle (English), 1927-1935, (3 folders) (Box 196)
      - Pond's, 1943 (Box 196)
      - Prince Matchabelli, 1935 (Box 196)
      - Princess Pat, 1928-1942, (5 folders) (Box 196)
      - Printemps, 1934 (Box 196)
      - Proker, 1934 (Box 196)
      - Revlon, 1944-1953, (3 folders) (Box 196)
      - Revlon, 1946-1952, (6 folders) (Box 197)
      - Roger and Gallet, 1940 (Box 197)
      - Rose Laird, 1934 (Box 197)
      - Helena Rubenstein, 1927-1951, (18 folders) (Box 197)
      - Scandia Jourde, 1930-1931 (Box 198)
      - J. Schaeffer, 1928-1931, (3 folders) (Box 198)
      - Sempre Giovine, 1912-1925 (Box 198)
      - Seventeen, 1930-1933 (Box 198)
      - Tangee, 1927-1940, (6 folders) (Box 198)
      - Terra Derma Lax, 1922-1923 (Box 198)
      - Tone, 1941 (Box 198)
      - Tussy, 1944-1953, (9 folders) (Box 198)
      - Lucretia Vanderbilt, 1928-1929 (Box 198)
      - Westmore, 1943 (Box 198)
      - Woodbury, 1931-1942, (6 folders) (Box 198)
      - Yardley, 1943 (Box 198)
    - Rouge
      - Carrot Rouge, 1925 (Box 198)
      - Djer Kiss, 1920-1925 (Box 198)
      - Richard Hudnut (including DuBarry Success School), 1954 (Box 198)
      - Jarnac, 1925 (Box 198)
      - Jonteel, 1920 (Box 198)
      - Mad Cap, 1922-1923 (Box 198)
      - Pert, 1925-1926 (Box 198)
      - Po-Go, 1925-1938 (Box 198)
      - Princess Pat, 1922-1940, (2 folders) (Box 198)
      - Pum-kin, 1926-1927 (Box 198)
      - Rouge Incarnat, 1929-1930 (Box 198)
      - Helena Rubenstein, 1922 (Box 198)
      - Tangee, 1924-1927 (Box 198)
      - Tre-Jur, 1924-1925 (Box 198)
      - White Rouge, 1928-1930 (Box 198)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1922 (Box 198)
    - Beauty Specialists and Beauty Preparations, 1924-1939, (8 folders) (Box 199)
    - Eye Preparations--Maybelline, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 199)
    - Sanitary Pads
      - Meds, 1940-1953, (9 folders) (Box 200)
      - Modess (Johnson & Johnson), 1927-1942, (13 folders) (Box 200)
      - San-Nap-Pak, 1943-1953, (11 folders) (Box 200)
      - Tampax, 1946-1953, (8 folders) (Box 200)
      - Curity, 1943 (Box 201)
      - Delnaps, 1920-1934, (5 folders) (Box 201)
      - Feminix, 1925 (Box 201)
      - Fibs, 1943-1952, (10 folders) (Box 201)
      - Kotex, 1943-1953, (10 folders) (Box 201)
      - Parapad, 1924 (Box 201)
      - Swanfleece, 1928 (Box 201)
      - Venus, 1932-1942 (Box 201)
      - Veldoun, 1929-1931, (2 folders) (Box 202)
      - Wix, 1937-1938 (Box 202)
      - Holly-Pax, 1938-1942 (Box 202)
      - Miscellaneous, 1924-1954, (14 folders) (Box 202)
      - Beltx, 1929-1930 (Box 202)
      - Faultless, 1928 (Box 202)
    - Shaving Preparations
      - Miscellaneous (Razors), 1954 (Box 202)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (3 folders) (Box 202)
    - Shaving Cream
      - Miscellaneous, 1918-1928, (2 folders) (Box 202)
      - Barbasol, 1922-1939, (11 folders) (Box 202)
      - Burma-Shave, 1947-1951, (2 folders) (Box 202)
      - Colgates, 1948-1953, (2 folders) (Box 202)
      - Colgates, 1935-1946, (5 folders) (Box 203)
      - Bauer and Black, 1919-1921 (Box 203)
      - Brisk, 1929-1930 (Box 203)
      - Coty, 1931 (Box 203)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Soap (toilet)
      - Ivory, 1926-1942 (Box 203)
      - Jap Rose, 1928-1930, (3 folders) (Box 203)
      - Kirkman, 1937-1945, (5 folders) (Box 203)
      - Kirk's, 1927-1934, (6 folders) (Box 203)
      - Lanchere, 1928-1930, (2 folders) (Box 203)
      - Lana Oil, 1925 (Box 203)
      - Larkin, 1922 (Box 203)
      - Lifebuoy, 1939-1952, (4 folders) (Box 203)
      - Murphy's Oil (for house), 1931 (Box 203)
      - Octagon, 1928-1932, (2 folders) (Box 203)
      - Olva, 1925-1928 (Box 203)
      - Palmolive, 1925-1933, (2 folders) (Box 203)
      - Pall Mall, 1933-1935, (2 folders) (Box 203)
      - Pears, 1920-1937 (Box 203)
      - Peets Crystal White, 1919 (Box 204)
      - Pine Tree, 1931 (Box 204)
      - Plantol, 1925 (Box 204)
      - Resinol, 1922-1927, (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - Roger Gallet, 1933-1935, (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - Swan, 1941 (Box 204)
      - Sweetheart, 1928-1948, (11 folders) (Box 204)
    - Institutional
      - Proctor & Gamble, 1949-1952, (3 folders) (Box 204)
    - Soap (toilet)
      - Tag, 1939 (Box 205)
      - Woodbury, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 205)
      - Wrisley's, 1944-1951, (7 folders) (Box 205)
      - Yardley, 1941 (Box 205)
      - Zanol, 1929 (Box 205)
      - Miscellaneous, 1934-1954, (15 folders) (Box 205)
    - Water Softeners
      - Climaline, Oaklite, etc., 1953 (Box 205)
    - Dentrifices
      - Pepsodent, 1927-1936, (5 folders) (Box 206)
      - Squibb, 1925-1947, (5 folders) (Box 206)
      - Squibb, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 207)
      - Stera-kleen, 1935-1942, (5 folders) (Box 207)
      - Strasska's, 1930 (Box 207)
      - Teel, 1939-1949, (9 folders) (Box 207)
      - Vivomint, 1920-1921 (Box 207)
      - Worcester, 1933-1938, (2 folders) (Box 207)
      - Williams, 1927 (Box 207)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1952, (12 folders) (Box 207)
    - Hair Preparations
      - Brownatone, 1943-1946 (Box 207)
      - Conti Castile, 1927-1951, (16 folders) (Box 208)
      - Coty, 1933-1934 (Box 208)
      - Cleero, 1925 (Box 208)
      - Helene Curtis, 1951-1953, (3 folders) (Box 208)
      - Danderine, 1920-1952, (10 folders) (Box 208)
      - Drene, 1946-1950, (4 folders) (Box 208)
      - Dr. Dick's, 1928-1931 (Box 208)
      - Duart, 1935-1937 (Box 208)
      - Edens Wave, 1933 (Box 208)
      - Eugene, 1932-1934 (Box 208)
      - Fitch's, 1935-1953, (17 folders) (Box 209)
      - Ferond's, 1920 (Box 209)
      - Farr's, 1930-1932, (7 folders) (Box 209)
      - Grayban, 1932-1933 (Box 209)
      - Glo Co, 1929-1934 (Box 209)
      - Glorilox, 1925 (Box 209)
      - Glostora, 1927-1943, (2 folders) (Box 209)
      - Glover's, 1928-1953, (21 folders) (Box 209)
      - Godefry's, 1932-1933, (2 folders) (Box 209)
      - Golden Glint, 1927-1941, (5 folders) (Box 209)
      - Liquid Hair Groom, 1930 (Box 209)
      - Miscellaneous, 1928-1930, (3 folders) (Box 209)
      - Mary T. Goldman's, 1931-1949, (15 folders) (Box 210)
      - Gray's, 1938 (Box 210)
      - Halo, 1939-1952, (10 folders) (Box 210)
      - Kolor Bak, 1927-1933, (2 folders) (Box 210)
      - Harper Method, 1936 (Box 210)
      - Richard Hudnut, 1948 (Box 210)
      - Henna Tint, Henne Linine, Henalea, Hennafoam, 1921-1926 (Box 210)
      - Hennafoam, 1929-1942 (Box 210)
      - Brownatone, 1927-1941, (3 folders) (Box 210)
      - Brylcreem, 1939 (Box 210)
      - Canute, 1937-1942, (3 folders) (Box 211)
      - Caroco, 1923-1924 (Box 211)
      - Chamberlain, 1934 (Box 211)
      - Brylcreem, 1938 (Box 211)
      - Icilma, 1928 (Box 211)
      - Jane Curran, 1930 (Box 211)
      - Jeris, 1944-1948, (2 folders) (Box 211)
      - Jo Cur, 1939 (Box 211)
      - Kep, 1941 (Box 211)
      - Kreml, 1927-1953, (8 folders) (Box 211)
      - Inecto Rapid Notox, 1935-1940, (4 folders) (Box 211)
      - Lemon Rinse, 1927-1931 (Box 211)
      - Laco, 1928-1953, (7 folders) (Box 211)
      - LaVay, 1930 (Box 211)
      - La Geradine, 1932-1935, (2 folders) (Box 211)
      - Liquid Arvon, 1927-1933 (Box 211)
      - Lorraine, 1924 (Box 211)
      - Lovalon, 1937-1953, (8 folders) (Box 211)
      - Lustre-Crème, 1950-1953 (Box 211)
      - Marcelle/Brilliantine de France, 1924-1928, (2 folders) (Box 211)
      - Marchand's, 1944-1953, (10 folders) (Box 211)
      - Marlene's Hair Waving Shampoo, 1952 (Box 211)
      - Clairol, 1948-1949 (Box 211)
      - Vitalis, 1928-1934, (5 folders) (Box 212)
      - White Rain, 1953 (Box 212)
      - Miscellaneous, 1918-1944, (8 folders) (Box 212)
      - Dreme, 1947 (Box 212)
      - Clairol, 1947 (Box 212)
      - Coffelt's, 1937 (Box 212)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1955, (11 folders) (Box 213)
      - Articles on hair, 1924-1928 (Box 214)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1953, (7 folders) (Box 214)
      - Permanents, Waves, 1954 (Box 214)
      - Hair curlers, 1935 (Box 214)
      - Hair pins, nets, etc., 1927-1934, (3 folders) (Box 214)
      - Hair dryers, 1927-1928 (Box 214)
  - Automobiles--Trucks
    - Autocar, 1946-1953, (6 folders) (Box 214)
    - Chrysler, 1946-1953, (6 folders) (Box 214)
    - Diamond T, 1945-1953, (8 folders) (Box 215)
    - Dodge, 1945-1953, (9 folders) (Box 215)
    - Federal, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 215)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet, 1951-1953, (3 folders) (Box 215)
    - International Harvester, 1953 (Box 215)
    - International Harvester, 1947-1952, (6 folders) (Box 216)
    - Mack, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 216)
    - REO, 1948-1952, (4 folders) (Box 216)
    - Studebaker, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 216)
    - White, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 216)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 216)
    - Accessories/Parts
      - Antifreeze, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 216)
      - Antifreeze, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 217)
      - Bearings, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 217)
      - Chains, 1948-1954, (5 folders) (Box 217)
      - Express transportation, 1949-1954, (5 folders) (Box 217)
      - Spark plugs
        - A-C, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 217)
        - Autolite, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 217)
        - Champion, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 217)
        - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954 (Box 217)